Guide to the Solomon Sir Jones Films
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Original films
  - Film 11, 1925, undated; (390 feet) (Box 11 (Original))
    - Colonial Bungalow of Mr. and Mrs. Granger, 507 North 9th Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 1; 00:11:02 - 00:11:26
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. Ed. Guiwn, 903 North 9th Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 1; 00:11:27 - 00:12:07
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. W. V. Hewitt, 552 North 5th Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 1; 00:12:08 - 00:12:27
    - Mrs. M. Jones building at 231 South 2nd Street, "Call by", Muskogee, OK, 1925 October 11; 00:12:28 - 00:13:08
    - A few scenes at the Oklahoma Free State Fair, Muskogee, OK, 1925 October 10; 00:13:09 - 00:15:24
  - Film 12, undated; (352 feet) (Box 12 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.5-2.0%, 20 splices many ripped perforations, large section about 100 feet unusable because of pulled perforations, emulsion peel.
    - Where Christ mounted the ass to ride and Reverend S.S. Jones taking hat off, Jerusalem, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:00:47
    - Where Christ taught his Disciples to pray Jerusalem, undated; 00:00:48 - 00:01:12
    - Overlooking Jerusalem from top of Mt. Olive Jerusalem, undated; 00:01:13 - 00:01:17
    - Christian Street in Jerusalem, undated; 00:01:18 - 00:08:16
    - City of Nazareth in Galilee Holy Land, undated; 00:08:17 - 00:10:06
    - Shepherds with their flocks in Galilee Holy Land, undated; 00:10:07 - 00:10:26
  - Film 13, 1925, undated; (314 feet) (Box 13 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.6-1.8%, 35 splices, some ripped perforations, some torn frames, some burned frames, 3 feet section all perforations broken.
    - Woolworth Tower and 5th Ave, New York City, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:00:36
    - Over in Brooklyn, New York City, undated; 00:00:37 - 00:01:22
    - Washington Monument [Washington Square Arch] and Madison Square, New York City, undated; 00:01:23 - 00:02:14
    - Reverend H. T. Borders, undated; 00:02:15 - 00:02:25
    - Street scenes, New York City, undated; 00:02:26 - 00:02:57
    - Reverend H. T. Borders, undated; 00:02:58 - 00:03:09
    - Train at station, undated; 00:03:10 - 00:03:51
    - Professor W. H. Fort of Okmulgee come to meet his pastor as he reached America, undated; 00:03:52 - 00:04:09
    - Honorary Dungee of the Black Dispatch and Mrs. Huston leaving Dr. Jones's home, undated; 00:04:10 - 00:04:51
    - Muskogee ministers and wives receiving Dr. Jones from abroad, undated; 00:04:52 - 00:05:25
    - Dr. L. Drane pastor of Friendship Baptist Church, Chicago, IL, undated; 00:05:26 - 00:05:39
    - T. J. Elliot's department store, Muskogee, OK, undated; 00:05:40 - 00:06:21
    - Mademoiselle C. J. Walker's S. W. Headquarters, Mrs. Dora Stevens, 509 Katy Avenue, Muskogee, OK, undated; 00:06:22 - 00:06:51
    - M. T. H. School and Team Basketball Boys and Girls, undated; 00:06:52 - 00:10:01
    - Their present $40,000 home near Bristow, OK, 1925; 00:10:02 -00:10:07
      Includes no footage, was perhaps too damaged
    - Muskogee 2nd Street North and South, Elliott Building and People's Hotel and Café, Muskogee, OK, undated; 00:10:08 - 00:11:20
    - Mademoiselle C. J. Walker's S. W. Headquarters, Mrs. Dora Stevens, 509 Katy Avenue, Muskogee, OK, undated; 00:11:21 - 00:11:43
  - Film 14, undated; (380 feet) (Box 14 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.5-1.6%, 31 splices, a lot of ripped perforations, torn frames, some taped splices, some burned frames, several sections pulled perforations on both sides, punctured sections by sprockets.
    - Waterfront in Switzerland, 00:00:00 - 00:00:12
    - Our baggage laving hotel, D. Angleterre in Switzerland, 00:00:13 - 00:00:46
    - Train station, 00:00:46 - 00:00:21
    - Steamer Heleon in Adriatic Sea, 00:01:22 - 00:01:31
    - Sea front in Trieste, Italy, 00:01:32 - 00:02:06
    - Jews returning to Jerusalem, Zion Movement, 00:02:07 00:02:23
    - Shots of town streets from ship or train, shots of family, 00:02:24 - 00:03:53
    - Palm trees in Africa, 00:03:54 - 00:04:27
    - "Natives in Northern Africa", 00:04:28 - 00:05:15
    - Port Said in Egypt, 00:05:16 - 00:05:40
    - Sailors from Bombay, India parading in Egypt, 00:05:41 - 00:06:06
    - David Street in Jerusalem, 00:06:07 - 00:07:55
    - Jacob's Well at Shechem in Sameria, 00:07:56 - 00:08:22
    - Hill of Cursing and Hill of Blessing, 00:08:23 - 00:09:30
    - Mt. Carmel where Elijah called down fire, 00:09:31 - 00:10:02
    - In Haifa West Galilee, Haifa street scene, 00:10:03 - 00:10:48
    - Mission School by an American woman, 00:10:49 - 00:13:30
  - Film 15, 1926, undated; (410 feet) (Box 15 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.0-1.5%, 27 splices, some taped splices, some ripped perforations, torn off perforation section.
    - No description, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:05:05
    - Booker T. Washington School from first to 11th grades, Mrs. A. L. Locust Principal, Haskell, OK, 1926 February 16; 00:05:06 - 00:06:46
    - Boys Basketball and the Proficient Faculty, Haskell, OK, 1926 February 16; 00:06:47 - 00:07:43
    - Washington School basketball team Princast and Patrons in action, Coweta, OK, 1926 February 16; 00:07:44 - 00:09:01
    - Professor and Mrs. Hill, their family, home, store, Gibson Station, OK, 1926 February 24; 00:09:02 - 00:09:23
    - Professor R. D. F. Hill, his teachers and the girls who won State Prize for spelling, Gibson Station, OK, 1926 January 18; 00:09:24 - 00:10:52
    - Public School at Checotah, Professor M. B. Bryant and Mrs. Madge Hanna, Teachers, Checotah, OK, 1926 January 14; 00:10:53 - 00:11:30
    - Boynton Colored High School, classes, faculty, students, Superintendent W. T. Whitman (all grades) Boynton, OK, 1926 January 15; 00:11:31 - 00:11:35
      No footage, maybe removed due to damage
    - Boynton School in action from the 1st to the 10th [grades], Prof. P. W. Watman, Principal, 1926 January 15; 00:11:26 - 00:15:13
      Students are dancing and skipping
  - Film 16, 1925-1927, undated; (468 feet) (Box 16 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.0-1.5%, 29 splices, some taped splices, many sections punctured by sprocket, some torn frames, some burned frames, several ripped perforations 5 feet section unusable torn and pulled perforations.
    - Mrs. D. H. Wilson Sharp, hemstitching and dressmaking, 507 East 5th,Okmulgee, OK, 1926 March 3; 00:00:00 - 00:01:24
    - Reverend Dr. S. S. Jones, Muskogee, OK, 1924 December; 00:01:25 - 00:02:09
    - Antioch Church, Muskogee, Dr. Jones, Pastor, Muskogee OK, 1924 December; 00:02:10 - 00:04:47
    - Olympia S. M. School and Parents Tea Club Student Christmas Tree, Professor J. I. Wallace, Principal, 1927 December 23; 00:04:48 - 00:05:56
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. M. Broner, only 5 years in Oklahoma from Sherman, Texas, Wetumka, OK, 1925 October 9; 00:05:57 - 00:06:28
    - Cozy Café family and home cooking, Mrs. Annie Barnett and Mrs. Curry, Proprietor Wetumka, OK, 1925 October 9; 00:06:29 - 00:08:13
      Footage of a hair and nail salon
    - Residence of Mrs. M. Brooks 804 5th Street, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 October 8; 00:08:14 - 00:09:08
    - Home of my lamented dear L. McGlauthing, Wife and Daughter, 500 North Muskogee Street, Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:09:09 - 00:09:35
    - Mr. and Mrs. G. T. King's Residence 520 North Porter Avenue, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 July 31; 00:09:36 - 00:10:00
    - Fifth Street looking east Okmulgee, OK, 1925 July 31; 00:10:01 - 00:10:53
    - Residence of Honorable J. Coody Johnson and wife, S. Seminole St.,Wewoka, OK, 1925 August 12; 00:10:54 - 00:11:14
    - Dr. J. J. Chandler's Building, 215 Wewoka Avenue, Wewoka, OK, 1925 August 12; 00:11:15 - 00:11:41
    - W. E. Chandler Ph. C. Building, 210 Wewoka Avenue, Wewoka, OK, 1925 August 12; 00:11:42 - 00:12:16
    - The Stevenson MFG. Co. Junior Department, Wewoka, OK, 1925 August 13; 00:12:17 - 00:12:37
    - Residence of Mrs. S. A. Miller and Son, West Cedar Street, Wewoka, OK, 1925 August 13; 00:12:38 - 00:13:05
    - First farm home of Mr. and Mrs. H. Miller, year 1906 near Wewoka, OK, 1925 August 13; 00:13:06 - 00:13:29
    - Second farm home of Mr. and Mrs. H. Miller, year 1917 near Wewoka, OK, 1925 August 13; 00:13:30 - 00:14:04
    - Mrs. D. R.. Chandler and Daughter, 114 South Seminole Street, Wewoka, OK, 1925 August 13; 00:14:05 - 00:14:20
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. S. C. Carson, W. Apple St. Contractor and Builders, Wewoka, OK, 1925 August 12; 00:14:21 - 00:14:56
    - Helen Smith, age 14, caused by fever, will you help her, Holdenville, OK, undated; 00:14:57 - 00:15:14
    - Breakfast at the SW C and S Association, Reverend C. Johnson, Mod. Professor W. H. Fort Clerk, Holdenville, OK, 1925 August 14; 00:15:15 - 00:15:58
    - Dunbar High School Professor. N. J. Caesar, principal his teachers, Shawnee, OK, 1925 September 25; 00:15:59 - 00:16:51
    - Reverend M. L. Hatchett and wife and son, pastor, New Hope Baptist Church, Vernon, OK, 1925 October 7; 00:16:52 - 00:17:15
  - Film 17, 1926-1927, undated; (450 feet) (Box 17 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.2-1.4%, 150 feet is orange based print stock, 18 splices, pulled perforations on both sides, many burned frames, 4 1 feet section with ripped perforations, some taped splices.
    - Private boarding house of Mrs. W. E. Strickland Hightow, stop by Langston, OK, 1926 May 28; 00:00:00 - 00:01:01
    - Douglass High School, seniors and faculty, Mrs. L. L. Sawner, principal, Chandler, OK, 1926 May 5; 00:01:02 - 00:02:39
      Physical education exercises
    - Needlepoint group, Chandler, undated; 00:02:40 - 00:04:07
    - G. U. O. of O. F. and H. of R. in parade to sermon, J. F. Burton and E. Wade, Muskogee, OK, 1927 May 9; 00:04:08 - 00:07:05
    - State Spelling Bee for Negroes by K. of P. and the Education Board of Oklahoma, Dr. C. B. Wickham at Calvary Baptist Church North East 2nd, Oklahoma City, OK, 1927; 00:07:06 - 00:09:31
    - Inserted: Adventure Series No. 2, Produced by Major Hammond World Explorer, Sole Distributors Bell and Howell Co. Chicago IL; "Capturing Big Fish in Pacific Waters", undated; 00:09:32 - 00:16:36
  - Film 18, 1925-1926, undated; (432 feet) (Box 18 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.0-1.5%, 40 splices, emulsion peel, burned frames, several ripped perforations.
    - Inserted: Adventure Series No. 2, Produced by Major Hammond World Explorer, Sole Distributors Bell and Howell Co. Chicago IL; "Capturing Big Fish in Pacific Waters", undated; 00:00:00 - 00:00:28
    - First Church Baptizing 71 candidates, Dr. S. S. Jones, Pastor, Okmulgee, OK, 1926 February; 00:00:29 - 00:03:21
    - Mann Drug Co.,Where You Are Home, 413 E. 5th Street, Okmulgee, OK, 1926 April 5; 00:03:22 - 00:04:09
    - Delaware Hotel, hot and cold baths, corner of 4th de Ware, P. H. Benson Proprietor, Okmulgee, OK, 1926 May 3; 00:04:10 - 00:04:51
    - S. D. Hooker Dry Goods Co. 123 North Greenwood Street, Tulsa, OK, undated; 00:04:52 - 00:05:20
    - Tulsa Business League entertaining Dr. S.S. Jones, noon luncheon, Tulsa, OK, undated; 00:05:21 - 00:06:03
      Jones is in the eyeglasses
    - Mt. Zion Baptist Church after the riot, Tulsa, OK, undated; 00:06:04 - 00:07:55
      Footage of photographs
    - Greenwood Street, Tulsa, OK, undated; 00:07:56 - 00:08:38
    - C.B. Bottling Works, 528 E. Archie, Tulsa, OK, undated; 00:08:39 - 00:10:20
    - Jackson's Undertaking Co., Tulsa, OK, undated; 00:10:21 - 00:11:01
    - Booker T. Washington High School, noon hour, Tulsa, OK, undated; 00:11:02 - 00:12:08
    - Dunbar Grade School, Tulsa, OK, undated; 00:12:09 - 00:12:47
    - Dunbar Agriculture Gardens, Tulsa, OK, undated; 00:12:48 - 00:13:58
    - State High Y's in Session (Manuel High), Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:13:59 - 00:15:43
    - Pilgrims at River Jordan where Christ was baptized, undated; 00:15:44 - 00:16:03
  - Film 19, 1925, undated; (451 feet) (Box 19 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.2-1.4%, 36 splices, few taped splices, several burned and torn frames.
    - Big masonic funeral at Church, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:05:47
      Meeting at Church Headquarters (Convention) Indianapolis, IN; Madam C. J. Walker display and Reps. Indianapolis, IN
    - Dr. Lot and Asst. Sec. Taylor and their wives National Baptist Convention, Kansas City, MO, 1925 September 14; 00:05:48 - 00:06:55
    - Dr. G. W. Williams and Ohio Del. at National Baptist Convention, Kansas City, MO, 1925 September 14; 00:06:56 - 00:07:21
    - Dr. H. J. Gooden and New Orleans Del. At National Baptist Convention, Kansas City, MO, 1925 September 14; 00:07:22 - 00:07:45
    - Grand Officers with Scouts and Juvenile Background, undated; 00:07:46 - 00:08:13
    - Auto Collision at State and 30th Street, Chicago, IL, 1925 September 4; 00:08:14 - 00:08:49
    - Looking west on Adam Street, Chicago, IL, undated; 00:08:50 - 00:09:02
    - Corner of Michigan and Adam Streets, Chicago, IL, undated; 00:09:03 - 00:09:29
    - Auto Parking Station, Lake Michigan looking east, Chicago, IL, undated; 00:09:30 - 00:09:56
    - State and Monroe Streets, busiest comer in the world, Chicago, IL, undated; 00:09:57 - 00:10:32
    - Dr. and Mrs. Drane's home on Warren St., Chicago, IL, undated; 00:10:33 - 00:11:31
    - Friendship Baptist Church, Dr. Drane's Tenth Anniversary, Chicago, IL, 1925 May; 00:11:32 - 00:15:17
    - Washington Building and Western Avenue, Chicago, IL, undated; 00:15:18 - 00:15:35
    - Illinois River, Chicago, IL, undated; 00:15:36 - 00:16:11
    - Ft. Madison and Mississippi River's back waters from Keokuk Dam Fort, Madison, Iowa, undated; 00:16:12 - 00:16:50
  - Film 20, 1925; (440 feet) (Box 20 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.2-1.6%, 37 splices, few taped splices, several burned and torn frames, pulled perforations.
    - Dr. G. H. Mitchell Nat Evangelist and soul saver, and Arlander, the boy preacher, Kansas City, MO, 1925 August 24; 00:00:00 - 00:00:16
    - Grand Lodge of U. B. F. and S. M. T. annual parade, Honorary P. Delancy GM, Boley, OK, 1925 August 27; 00:00:17 - 00:01:06
    - UBF and SMT No.58 Drill Contest Mrs. Bes Taylor and Mrs. E. O. Bacon MM, Boley, OK, 1925 August 27; 00:01:07 - 00:04:29
    - Headquarters Security Life Insurance Co. and a few of its officers, Tulsa, OK, 1925 August 20; 00:04:30 - 00:05:24
    - Industrial Parade of National Negro Business League, Tulsa, OK, 1925 August 20; 00:05:25 - 00:07:40
    - Tenth U. S. Calvary Band from Ft. Huachuca, Arizona, W. H. Hammon, Manager, Tulsa, OK, 1925 August 20; 00:07:41 - 00:08:09
    - Officers of National Negro Business League, Honorable R. R. Moton, President, Mr. A. L. Holsey Secretary, Tulsa, OK, 1925 August 21; 00:08:10 - 00:08:24
      Dr. Robert R. Moton with hat
    - Honorable Bert M. Roddy, Mr. Lester Walton, Mrs. M. J. Wright and Mrs. L. R. Dickerson at National Business League, Tulsa, OK, 1925 August 21; 00:08:25 - 00:08:44
    - D. B. and O. Institute, Professor J. R. Johnson Superintendent, Taft, OK, 1925 August 22; 00:08:45 - 00:09:04
    - Superintendent residence his wife and Dr. R. R. Moton of Tuskegee, Fred R. Moore, NY and President I. W. Young of Langston, Taft, OK, 1925 August 22; 00:09:05 - 00:09:34
    - Industrial Home for Girls, Taft, OK, 1925 August 22; 00:09:35 - 00:10:06
    - Hospital, Taft, OK, 1925 August 22; 00:10:07 - 00:10:21
    - Girls Dormitory, Taft, OK, 1925 August 22; 00:10:22 - 00:10:46
    - Boys Dormitory, Taft, OK, 1925 August 22; 00:10:47 - 00:11:10
    - Girls Annex, Taft, OK, 1925 August 22; 00:11:11 - 00:11:33
    - Bird's eye view of Taft School, Taft, OK, 1925 August 22; 00:11:34 - 00:12:01
      President I.W. Young, center
    - National Business League Parade, Guest of Muskogee League, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 22; 00:12:02 - 00:15:42
    - Jackson, who murdered Algen Leeks near Taft OK, arresting officers at Taft Jail, Taft, OK, 1925 September 30; 00:15:43 - 00:16:11
  - Film 21, 1925, undated; (418 feet) (Box 21 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.5-1.6%, 34 splices, some ripped perforations, some taped splices.
    - Nurse at hospital and other footage, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:00:34
    - Colored Library, Okmulgee OK, 1925 July 31; 00:00:35 - 00:00:57
    - Residence of Mr. P. M. Mann, 1017 East 3rd, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 July 31; 00:00:58 - 00:01:24
    - Mr. and Mrs. I. C. Copeland, Residence 1002 East 3rd Street, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 July 31; 00:01:25 - 00:01:57
    - Dr. R. B. Taylor's Residence, 1015 East 3rd Street, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 July 31; 00:01:58 - 00:02:30
    - Mr. and Mrs. T. M. Bruner Residence, 721 North Central Avenue, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 July 31; 00:02:31 - 00:02:40
    - B. H. Russell Grocery and Market and Filling Station, Delaware and 5th Street, Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:02:41 - 00:03:49
    - Residence of Attorney J. C. Evans and wife, 101 East 3rd Street, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 July 28; 00:03:50 - 00:04:21
    - Attucks Grade School, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 July 31; 00:04:22 - 00:04:48
    - Hospital No. 2 Staff and Board, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 July 31; 00:04:49 - 00:05:01
    - Macedonia Burial and Aid Association, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 June 21; 00:05:02 - 00:05:56
    - Madame Camper Hairdresser, Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:05:57 - 00:06:13
    - Creek Indians and Natives in Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:06:14 - 00:06:31
    - O. Douglas Mercantile and Market "They Satisfy All", Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:06:32 - 00:07:30
    - Mr. and Mrs. William Shealey, Prize Winning White Rocks, 1114 East 1st St, Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:07:31 - 00:08:58
    - Mr. W. M. Pierce and S. Scott's home in Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:08:59 - 00:09:21
    - Going to mother's and grandmother's, Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:09:22 - 00:09:36
    - Going to church, Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:09:37 - 00:12:21
    - Attorney D. J. Wallace and wife Mrs. D. D. Wallace Residence, Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:12:22 - 00:12:48
    - Professor P. W. Watman, [6??] North Porter Avenue, Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:12:49 - 00:13:31
    - Dr. A. L. Wallace and wife, 601 North Porter Avenue, Okmulgee, OK, undated; 00:13:22 - 00:13:51
    - The Pioneer Store Co., "Gen. Mchoes", Boynton, OK, undated; 00:13:52 - 00:14:37
    - Lockridge and Watley blacksmith and auto repair shop, Boynton, OK, 1925 July 20; 00:14:38 - 00:15:15
    - Mr. and Mrs. William Clark residence and store, 929 E. First Street, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 July 2; 00:15:16 - 00:15:21
      No footage, likely damaged and removed
  - Film 22, 1926, undated; (423 feet) (Box 22 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.0-1.5%, 31 splices, many ripped perforations, some taped splices, few ripped frames.
    - Footage of car accident and parade, including soldiers and cars, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:01:06
    - New State Shoe Shop, Corner of Second and Court, Tom Caruthers, Muskogee, OK, 1926 August 29; 00:01:07 - 00:01:54
    - Coleman's New Bakery and Café, making 1,000 loaves per day working 14 hands, 226 North Second Street, Muskogee, OK, 1926; 00:01:55 - 00:03:05
    - Coleman's Café Grocery and Fresh Fish Market Stop, Muskogee, OK, 1926 April 17; 00:03:06 - 00:04:09
    - Residence of Dr. H. L. Muckleroy, MD, 524 Terrace Boulevard, Muskogee, OK, 1926 May 8; 00:04:10 - 00:05:18
    - Muskogee Provident Hospital, Dr. H. L. Muckleroy Surgeon-in-Chief, Muskogee, OK, 1926 May 8; 00:05:19 - 00:05:56
    - Dunbar Ward School, May Day Exercise, Professor J. F. Cathey, Principal, Muskogee, OK, 1926 May 4; 00:05:57 - 00:07:02
    - Dr. E. H. Hilson of Texas and Antioch Baptist Gospel Team, Muskogee, OK, 1926 January 15; 00:07:03 - 00:09:49
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. J. J. Bruce, Corner of 9th and Market, Muskogee, OK, 1926 March 23; 00:09:50 - 00:11:08
    - First Baptist Church and Friends entering their new Edifice, Reverend J. W. King, Taft, OK, 1926 June 6; 00:11:09 - 00:12:19
    - Farm home of Mr. and Mrs. B. W. Long, Tullahassee, OK, 1926 June 6; 00:12:20 - 00:12:51
    - Footage includes National Baptist S. S. Congress banner; group of people on unidentified campus; people in a church; and a parade, undated; 00:12:52 - 00:15:59
  - Film 23, 1927, undated; (337 feet) (Box 23 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.3-1.6%, 27 splices, few ripped and pulled perforations.
    - Solomon Sir Jones, taking his hat off, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:00:05
    - Dunbar Consolidated High School, Professor G. M. Tuggles, faculty and students, Wellston, OK, 1927 March 4; 00:00:06 - 00:04:17
    - Funeral of Reverend Mrs. Lee Massey at First Baptist Church, Okmulgee, OK, 1927 March 10; 00:04:18 - 00:05:49
    - Mr. and Mrs. H. T. Hutton's Mercantile Store, Stop and See Them, 516 West Johnson Street, Sapulpa, OK, 1927 March 11; 00:05:50 - 00:06:18
    - J. E. King and C. D. Wilson Tailors and Cleaners, 502 West Johnson Street, Sapulpa OK, 1927 March 10; 00:06:19 - 00:06:47
    - Mr. B. H. Hancock U.S. Officer and City Patrol, call to Hutton Store, Sapulpa, OK, 1927 March 10; 00:06:48 - 00:07:07
    - Warn and Wilson Grocery and Friends, 506 West Johnson Street, Sapulpa, OK, 1927 March 10; 00:07:08 - 00:07:49
    - Smith Brothers Co. Electric and Battery, 107 North Marley, Drumright, OK, 1927 March 10; 00:07:50 - 00:08:31
    - State Teachers Association 19th Annual Session, Professor J. W. Hughes President, Muskogee, OK, 1927 February 10; 00:08:32 - 00:10:01
      Group photograph being taken
    - Booker T. Washington High School Professor L. J. Umstead Principal, El Reno, OK, 1927 March 2; 00:10:02 - 00:11:19
    - Tabernacle Baptist Church, Reverend E. W. Perry (Perry became President of the National Baptist Convention), D. D. Pastor, Oklahoma City, OK, 1927 March 4; 00:11:20 - 00:12:00
    - Edward Junk Yard (he became a home builder and opened a hospital), Oklahoma City, OK, undated; 00:12:01 - 00:12:37
  - Film 24, 1926-1928, undated; (473 feet) (Box 24 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.3-1.6%, 18 splices, few ripped and pulled perforations, some burned frames, some taped splices.
    - Dr. S. S. Jones, President of Con, visits Reverend E. D. Parker and family, Lawton, OK, 1927 April 8; 00:00:00 - 00:00:42
    - Galilee Baptist Church, Dr. E. D. Parker, Pastor and Dr. E. D. Parker baptizing his candidates, Lawton, OK, 1927 April 8 and 10; 00:00:43 - 00:02:36
    - Eighth Annual Session of Gen Bowen District Association All Department Reverend E. D. Parker, Mod., Lawton, OK, 1927 August 25; 00:02:37 - 00:04:28
    - Reverend A. J. Adkerson and wife at home in Wetumka, OK, 1928 August 16; 00:04:29 - 00:05:06
    - The funeral of Deacon H. A. Armstrong, Muskogee, OK, 1926 May; 00:05:07 - 00:09:01
    - Douglas High School and faculty, J. W. Sanford Superintendent (Sanford became President of Langston University) Ardmore, OK and Dunbar Ward School and faculty, J. W. Sanford Superintendent, Ardmore, OK, 1926 May 20; 00:09:02 - 00:11:38
    - Residence of Reverend and Mrs. I. P. Pittsfield 1309 8th Avenue North, East Ardmore, OK, 1926 May 20; 00:11:39 - 00:12:48
    - Mrs. S. L. Lampkins Rooms and Board, 217 W Pine Street, Cushing, OK, 1926 May 29; 00:12:49 - 00:13:19
    - A few of Mr. and Mrs. S. L. Lampkins Rent Houses, Cushing, OK, 1926 May 29; 00:13:20 - 00:13:41
    - Residence of Professor and Mrs. W. B. Jones of Lima, OK, 1926 June 3; 00:13:42 -00:14:05
    - Lima Public Schools Homer and Bruce Jones, contractors and builders, "Write them at" Lima, OK, 1926 June 3; 00:14:06 - 00:15:09
    - Dr. E. M. Maden of Polar Bluff visits Dr. W. C. Cartwright at St. Louis, MO, 1926 April 11; 00:15:10 - 00:15:39
    - The S. D. Hoover Co. Mail Order Department and a few St. Louis Salesmen P. Fin Building Street, St. Louis, MO, 1926 April 21; 00:15:40 - 00:16:53
    - Headquarters K of P of MO and some office, Force and Grand C. A. W. Lloyd at St. Louis, MO; Building foundation work and parade, Eufaula, OK, 1926 April 21; 00:16:54 - 00:17:30
  - Film 25, 1926-1927, undated; (307 feet) (Box 25 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.2-1.5%, 11 splices, some ripped and pulled perforations, some torn frames, few taped splices.
    - Corner stone laying, Eufaula, OK, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:03:43